import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const katakana: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"a\"?",
    "options": [
      "オ",
      "ア",
      "ワ",
      "ミ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ア"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ア\"?",
    "options": [
      "a",
      "u",
      "yo",
      "ra"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"i\"?",
    "options": [
      "チ",
      "ヘ",
      "イ",
      "ヨ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "イ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"イ\"?",
    "options": [
      "to",
      "ha",
      "i",
      "ya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "i"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"u\"?",
    "options": [
      "ハ",
      "ウ",
      "ヤ",
      "エ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ウ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ウ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ne",
      "ma",
      "ko",
      "u"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "u"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"e\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヲ",
      "ル",
      "オ",
      "エ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "エ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"エ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ru",
      "e",
      "na",
      "ma"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"o\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヤ",
      "マ",
      "オ",
      "ク"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "オ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"オ\"?",
    "options": [
      "o",
      "ni",
      "mu",
      "wa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "o"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ka\"?",
    "options": [
      "カ",
      "ツ",
      "キ",
      "ユ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "カ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"カ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ka",
      "u",
      "ro",
      "ku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ki\"?",
    "options": [
      "シ",
      "ソ",
      "キ",
      "リ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"キ\"?",
    "options": [
      "no",
      "nu",
      "ki",
      "re"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ki"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヤ",
      "メ",
      "ホ",
      "ク"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ク"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ク\"?",
    "options": [
      "ra",
      "ha",
      "ku",
      "ri"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ke\"?",
    "options": [
      "ソ",
      "シ",
      "ケ",
      "チ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ケ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ケ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ku",
      "wo",
      "na",
      "ke"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ke"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ko\"?",
    "options": [
      "ノ",
      "コ",
      "フ",
      "ヨ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "コ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"コ\"?",
    "options": [
      "mu",
      "ko",
      "tsu",
      "o"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ko"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"sa\"?",
    "options": [
      "サ",
      "ネ",
      "イ",
      "チ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "サ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"サ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ma",
      "yo",
      "sa",
      "hi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"shi\"?",
    "options": [
      "シ",
      "キ",
      "セ",
      "ハ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "シ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"シ\"?",
    "options": [
      "shi",
      "ma",
      "ni",
      "sa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"su\"?",
    "options": [
      "サ",
      "ス",
      "メ",
      "セ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ス"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ス\"?",
    "options": [
      "ru",
      "yu",
      "su",
      "u"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "su"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"se\"?",
    "options": [
      "セ",
      "ヒ",
      "キ",
      "サ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "セ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"セ\"?",
    "options": [
      "to",
      "o",
      "ri",
      "se"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "se"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"so\"?",
    "options": [
      "ル",
      "フ",
      "ワ",
      "ソ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ソ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ソ\"?",
    "options": [
      "se",
      "ro",
      "ya",
      "so"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ta\"?",
    "options": [
      "モ",
      "オ",
      "タ",
      "キ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "タ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"タ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ta",
      "ma",
      "wo",
      "se"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ta"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"chi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ハ",
      "タ",
      "チ",
      "セ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"チ\"?",
    "options": [
      "te",
      "chi",
      "ke",
      "re"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"tsu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ツ",
      "ム",
      "ケ",
      "カ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ツ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ツ\"?",
    "options": [
      "re",
      "no",
      "tsu",
      "a"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tsu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"te\"?",
    "options": [
      "ホ",
      "ト",
      "テ",
      "コ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "テ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"テ\"?",
    "options": [
      "te",
      "he",
      "ra",
      "yu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "te"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"to\"?",
    "options": [
      "ネ",
      "レ",
      "ラ",
      "ト"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ト"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ト\"?",
    "options": [
      "tsu",
      "to",
      "su",
      "ka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"na\"?",
    "options": [
      "ロ",
      "ナ",
      "イ",
      "キ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ナ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ナ\"?",
    "options": [
      "te",
      "ne",
      "ya",
      "na"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "na"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ni\"?",
    "options": [
      "レ",
      "ロ",
      "ネ",
      "ニ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ニ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ニ\"?",
    "options": [
      "to",
      "ni",
      "hi",
      "mu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ni"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"nu\"?",
    "options": [
      "レ",
      "ヌ",
      "ム",
      "テ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヌ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヌ\"?",
    "options": [
      "yo",
      "ru",
      "nu",
      "so"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "nu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ne\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヨ",
      "ス",
      "ネ",
      "シ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ネ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ネ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ne",
      "tsu",
      "su",
      "e"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ne"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"no\"?",
    "options": [
      "ネ",
      "ノ",
      "ウ",
      "ス"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ノ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ノ\"?",
    "options": [
      "na",
      "tsu",
      "no",
      "ho"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ha\"?",
    "options": [
      "ユ",
      "ハ",
      "シ",
      "コ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ハ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ハ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ri",
      "te",
      "ha",
      "mu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ha"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"hi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ム",
      "モ",
      "サ",
      "ヒ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヒ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヒ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hi",
      "i",
      "he",
      "so"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ラ",
      "ト",
      "ヒ",
      "フ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "フ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"フ\"?",
    "options": [
      "re",
      "fu",
      "ni",
      "to"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"he\"?",
    "options": [
      "メ",
      "フ",
      "ノ",
      "ヘ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヘ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヘ\"?",
    "options": [
      "na",
      "ri",
      "ne",
      "he"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "he"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ho\"?",
    "options": [
      "ウ",
      "ホ",
      "ハ",
      "ネ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ホ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ホ\"?",
    "options": [
      "na",
      "ma",
      "shi",
      "ho"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ho"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ma\"?",
    "options": [
      "ン",
      "マ",
      "ル",
      "ヘ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "マ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"マ\"?",
    "options": [
      "no",
      "yu",
      "ma",
      "ne"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"mi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ミ",
      "マ",
      "セ",
      "リ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ミ\"?",
    "options": [
      "me",
      "mi",
      "yo",
      "ro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"mu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヲ",
      "ワ",
      "ユ",
      "ム"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ム"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ム\"?",
    "options": [
      "mu",
      "ki",
      "me",
      "ko"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"me\"?",
    "options": [
      "キ",
      "ユ",
      "メ",
      "ネ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "メ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"メ\"?",
    "options": [
      "e",
      "me",
      "ra",
      "ru"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "me"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"mo\"?",
    "options": [
      "モ",
      "ト",
      "ナ",
      "ア"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "モ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"モ\"?",
    "options": [
      "i",
      "ro",
      "mo",
      "u"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ya\"?",
    "options": [
      "チ",
      "ユ",
      "ヤ",
      "コ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヤ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヤ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ke",
      "so",
      "ya",
      "mi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"yu\"?",
    "options": [
      "レ",
      "ヨ",
      "ユ",
      "ナ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ユ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ユ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ma",
      "te",
      "yu",
      "re"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "yu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"yo\"?",
    "options": [
      "カ",
      "ナ",
      "ヨ",
      "ケ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヨ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヨ\"?",
    "options": [
      "wa",
      "su",
      "to",
      "yo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "yo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ra\"?",
    "options": [
      "ム",
      "モ",
      "エ",
      "ラ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ラ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ラ\"?",
    "options": [
      "yo",
      "a",
      "ra",
      "ma"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ra"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ri\"?",
    "options": [
      "ニ",
      "タ",
      "リ",
      "キ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "リ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"リ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ri",
      "fu",
      "yu",
      "he"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ru\"?",
    "options": [
      "ス",
      "マ",
      "ル",
      "テ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ル"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ル\"?",
    "options": [
      "fu",
      "ru",
      "te",
      "ne"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ru"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"re\"?",
    "options": [
      "レ",
      "ネ",
      "ウ",
      "モ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "レ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"レ\"?",
    "options": [
      "mo",
      "ma",
      "ka",
      "re"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "re"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ro\"?",
    "options": [
      "ノ",
      "フ",
      "ロ",
      "ネ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ロ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ロ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ya",
      "se",
      "ro",
      "nu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"wa\"?",
    "options": [
      "ナ",
      "ワ",
      "ヲ",
      "タ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ワ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ワ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ka",
      "ma",
      "ho",
      "wa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"wo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヲ",
      "ン",
      "ホ",
      "ソ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヲ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヲ\"?",
    "options": [
      "shi",
      "te",
      "wo",
      "mi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"n\"?",
    "options": [
      "ン",
      "シ",
      "ヤ",
      "ホ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ン"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ン\"?",
    "options": [
      "yo",
      "n",
      "ro",
      "i"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "n"
  }
]

export default katakana;